var title = 'Traduza para grego. Inclua o artigo definido (ο, η, το...).';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "o Brasil",
   answer: ["η Βραζιλία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a Bélgica",
   answer: ["το Βέλγιο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Líbano",
   answer: ["ο Λίβανος", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a França",
   answer: ["η Γαλλία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Irã",
   answer: ["το Ιράν", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a América",
   answer: ["η Αμερική", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Canadá",
   answer: ["ο Καναδάς", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a Austrália",
   answer: ["η Αυστραλία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o México",
   answer: ["το Μεξικό", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a Rússia",
   answer: ["η Ρωσία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Marrocos",
   answer: ["το Μαρόκο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a Inglaterra",
   answer: ["η Αγγλία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];